I don't want to be cute or someone who needs
protecting. I want to be a man you can rely on.
It's all my fault.
Let me take care of you.
But I'm completely useless.
I really wanted to help.
Then how about taking a
computer certification test?
It'll boost your confidence.
I'll take it.
You know,
I really like Okumi-san.
That should be fine.
That's awesome!
We're getting an intern
at the company soon.
An intern?
You're going to be a mentor. Do your best!
Got it.
It's been a while.
Hideaki.
Huh?
What happened?
Water just sprayed everywhere.
Anyway, put on one
of my shirts for now.
Sorry about this.
"Are the Sexy Buttocks Not Good?"
(Episode 6)
Just my luck.
Excuse me, where is the
General Affairs Department?
Sorry.
You're changing.
Who are you?
Anyway, you should probably
put some clothes on first.
May I ask who you are?
I'm a junior at Kaiyo University.
Kujo Hiroto.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
So this is the intern
that's been talked about.
I need to work hard too.
That's Hizaki, right?
- Yeah.
- How old is he?
I think he's turning 23 this year.
Ai-chan. Let's go.
Ah!
You'd better not get too close to him.
I don't really care about gender.
But Hizaki might.
Oh yes, maybe so.
He might already be seeing someone.
Wait, he's seeing someone?
Ah, oh, uhh, erm, I
don't really know for sure.
So that means he might be single.
No good.
He's way too optimistic.
I look forward to working
with you starting today.
Likewise.
There's still a lot I don't know.
I hope to learn a lot from you.
If you don't mind.
Oh.
I'm actually acting like a proper mentor.
However...
Please check this over.
- You're already done?
- Yes.
You learn fast.
Do you need any help?
What!?
I'm already done.
(I really hate myself for
trying to act like a mentor.)
Hizaki-san.
('No one knows how to do it at first.')
(That's just empty talk to
someone who's actually capable.)
Hey, Kujo.
Why did you decide to
intern at our company?
Because I think it's a good company.
Plus, I have a relative working here.
- A relative?
- Yes.
I want to become someone like him.
I've looked up to him since I was a kid.
What a good kid.
Being stared at like that
makes my heart race.
Oh?
(I feel like this guy's reactions
are a lot like Okumi-san's.)
I heard the intern is
really attached to you?
Rather than attached,
it's more like we hit it off right away.
Once he officially joins,
he'll probably surpass me in no time.
You'll grow during that time too.
I hope so.
(There it is again.
The elder's perspective.)
(When will I ever be able to
make Okumi-san rely on me?)
Being stared at like that
makes my heart race.
Kujo is a bit like you, Okumi-san.
Well... actually,
He's my nephew.
My older sister's kid.
Oh.
Wait, why didn't you tell me?
You didn't tell me when you borrowed
someone else's shirt either.
I wasn't trying to hide
it from you on purpose.
Do I look like the kind
of guy who would cheat?
- Not at all.
- Then have a little more confidence.
You're right.
No, this is my own issue.
The time I spend with you
has a different meaning.
After all, I'm nearly fourty and divorced.
And you've only just become an adult.
So for your future,
rather than being with someone like me,
there's definitely someone better...
Ai-chan?
What's wrong? What is it?
What are you doing?
Ai-chan.
It's my turn today.
Eh?
Are my feelings
really that untrustworthy?
That's not what I meant.
Just be a good boy and accept my love.
I've never taken the lead before.
Don't be disappointed if I'm bad at it.
Not at all.
Wait, is this your first time?
Shut up. Yes.
First time in my life.
Why are you already hard?
The body is pretty honest, huh?
You're such a hopeless old man.
I can't even remember
the last time we took a walk.
You need to exercise properly.
You're right. I need to keep my stamina up.
I don't want you to hate me.
I would never hate you.
Besides, you were
pretty energetic last night.
So cute.
You really don't hold back
when it comes to this stuff, do you?
You have to speak your mind.
Just thinking 'I really like you' in
my head won't reach your heart.
You're really holding nothing back.
Because I made a mistake once before.
So I decided,
I will absolutely never
make the same mistake twice.
After all, neither my time nor yours
is infinite.
(Have I ever seriously told him
that I like him?)
(Can I just suddenly say,
'I like you too'?)
What's wrong?
(But I think I kind of get it now.)
After all, I'm the
second-generation successor.
Back then, I couldn't even worry
about whether I was gay or bisexual.
The time I spend with you
has a different meaning.
(Even though I still have a lot of
immature things to worry about,)
(Okumi-san has his own
insecurities and worries too.)
Sorry, hold on a second.
I also feel... for Okumi-san...
- Mom!
- Coming!
- Kids.
- Kids?
You're the president.
What about a successor?
- It's impossible if you're with me.
- I can't give birth either.
But I can stay by your side, Ai-chan.
And I can make you feel good
as many times as you want.
Horny old man.
Hey, what's wrong with that?
Hizaki-san and Hideaki?
(Even though it's sudden,)
(It's the company's busy season right now.)
I'm back.
It's really busy this time of year.
Yeah.
That being said, it's my first year too,
so it's my first time experiencing it.
(So he's his nephew.)
(Their vibes and everything
really are a bit similar, huh.)
Is there something on my face?
Nothing.
Just wondering what you're eating.
This? It looked
good, so I bought it.
Want a bite?
Can I?
- Go ahead, go ahead.
- Awesome.
Just a bite.
Say ah.
Ah.
Sorry about that.
I have a much younger brother,
so I just did it without thinking...
I brought the documents.
What's wrong?
Are you really that busy?
Do you have any stomach medicine?
- Huh?
- Ah...
Good work today.
- Good work.
- Hizaki-san, are you seeing anyone?
Huh?
(Next Episode Preview)
That person is super cute, right?
I'm going to get seriously mad.
I'm really glad you came,
but if you're busy, wouldn't it be
better to talk after you get home?
If it were me,
I would never make Hizaki-san cry.